{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648225975","data":{"timestamp":" 947648225975"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648227961","data":{"timestamp":" 947648227961"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648230257","data":{"timestamp":" 947648230257"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADITHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648232145","data":{"timestamp":" 947648232145"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648234719","data":{"timestamp":" 947648234719"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLINZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648236380","data":{"timestamp":" 947648236379"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648238726","data":{"timestamp":" 947648238726"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHEKECHEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648240424","data":{"timestamp":" 947648240424"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648242133","data":{"timestamp":" 947648242133"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648244510","data":{"timestamp":" 947648244510"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648246904","data":{"timestamp":" 947648246904"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAYATIMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648250977","data":{"timestamp":" 947648250977"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AGOSTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648253174","data":{"timestamp":" 947648253174"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648255077","data":{"timestamp":" 947648255077"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648257360","data":{"timestamp":" 947648257360"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648260040","data":{"timestamp":" 947648260040"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHUGHULI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648262185","data":{"timestamp":" 947648262185"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648264079","data":{"timestamp":" 947648264078"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648266123","data":{"timestamp":" 947648266123"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648268807","data":{"timestamp":" 947648268807"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLINZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648270663","data":{"timestamp":" 947648270663"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648273039","data":{"timestamp":" 947648273038"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASAIDIZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648274772","data":{"timestamp":" 947648274772"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648280388","data":{"timestamp":" 947648280388"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648282606","data":{"timestamp":" 947648282606"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHEKECHEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648286616","data":{"timestamp":" 947648286616"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyefika kwanza alikuwa Mkite wa umri wa mwaka mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEFIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648287826","data":{"timestamp":" 947648287825"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyefika kwanza alikuwa Mkite wa umri wa mwaka mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648290746","data":{"timestamp":" 947648290746"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyefika kwanza alikuwa Mkite wa umri wa mwaka mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648294076","data":{"timestamp":" 947648294076"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyefika kwanza alikuwa Mkite wa umri wa mwaka mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKITE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648296406","data":{"timestamp":" 947648296406"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyefika kwanza alikuwa Mkite wa umri wa mwaka mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648298196","data":{"timestamp":" 947648298196"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyefika kwanza alikuwa Mkite wa umri wa mwaka mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648299809","data":{"timestamp":" 947648299809"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyefika kwanza alikuwa Mkite wa umri wa mwaka mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648301570","data":{"timestamp":" 947648301570"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyefika kwanza alikuwa Mkite wa umri wa mwaka mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWAKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648303485","data":{"timestamp":" 947648303485"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyefika kwanza alikuwa Mkite wa umri wa mwaka mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648305509","data":{"timestamp":" 947648305509"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amebebwa katika lori la kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648307083","data":{"timestamp":" 947648307082"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amebebwa katika lori la kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEBEBWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648311421","data":{"timestamp":" 947648311421"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amebebwa katika lori la kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648313180","data":{"timestamp":" 947648313180"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amebebwa katika lori la kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648314855","data":{"timestamp":" 947648314855"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amebebwa katika lori la kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648316542","data":{"timestamp":" 947648316542"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amebebwa katika lori la kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648318493","data":{"timestamp":" 947648318492"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amebebwa katika lori la kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBICHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648325114","data":{"timestamp":" 947648325113"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLINZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648327085","data":{"timestamp":" 947648327084"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648329681","data":{"timestamp":" 947648329680"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASAIDIZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648331381","data":{"timestamp":" 947648331381"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648334054","data":{"timestamp":" 947648334054"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMWONEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648336194","data":{"timestamp":" 947648336194"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKITE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648338413","data":{"timestamp":" 947648338413"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HURUMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648340168","data":{"timestamp":" 947648340168"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648342305","data":{"timestamp":" 947648342305"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amekonda na mwenye huzuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648344502","data":{"timestamp":" 947648344502"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amekonda na mwenye huzuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEKONDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648346144","data":{"timestamp":" 947648346144"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amekonda na mwenye huzuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648347870","data":{"timestamp":" 947648347870"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amekonda na mwenye huzuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648349766","data":{"timestamp":" 947648349766"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amekonda na mwenye huzuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUZUNI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648353883","data":{"timestamp":" 947648353883"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini muda mfupi baadaye Mkite alikuwa mwenye afya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648355981","data":{"timestamp":" 947648355981"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini muda mfupi baadaye Mkite alikuwa mwenye afya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648357982","data":{"timestamp":" 947648357982"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini muda mfupi baadaye Mkite alikuwa mwenye afya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFUPI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648360027","data":{"timestamp":" 947648360027"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini muda mfupi baadaye Mkite alikuwa mwenye afya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADAYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648364825","data":{"timestamp":" 947648364825"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini muda mfupi baadaye Mkite alikuwa mwenye afya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKITE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648366865","data":{"timestamp":" 947648366864"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini muda mfupi baadaye Mkite alikuwa mwenye afya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648369295","data":{"timestamp":" 947648369295"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini muda mfupi baadaye Mkite alikuwa mwenye afya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648371980","data":{"timestamp":" 947648371980"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini muda mfupi baadaye Mkite alikuwa mwenye afya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AFYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648374347","data":{"timestamp":" 947648374347"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kucheza na wanyama wengine katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIANZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648376610","data":{"timestamp":" 947648376610"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kucheza na wanyama wengine katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648378356","data":{"timestamp":" 947648378356"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kucheza na wanyama wengine katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648380725","data":{"timestamp":" 947648380725"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kucheza na wanyama wengine katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648382889","data":{"timestamp":" 947648382888"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kucheza na wanyama wengine katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648385315","data":{"timestamp":" 947648385315"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kucheza na wanyama wengine katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648388246","data":{"timestamp":" 947648388245"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kucheza na wanyama wengine katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHEKECHEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648391817","data":{"timestamp":" 947648391817"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku nyingine katika mwezi huo wa Agosti helikopta ilitua mbele ya chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648394171","data":{"timestamp":" 947648394171"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku nyingine katika mwezi huo wa Agosti helikopta ilitua mbele ya chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGINE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648396291","data":{"timestamp":" 947648396291"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku nyingine katika mwezi huo wa Agosti helikopta ilitua mbele ya chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648398579","data":{"timestamp":" 947648398579"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku nyingine katika mwezi huo wa Agosti helikopta ilitua mbele ya chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648400215","data":{"timestamp":" 947648400215"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku nyingine katika mwezi huo wa Agosti helikopta ilitua mbele ya chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648402018","data":{"timestamp":" 947648402018"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku nyingine katika mwezi huo wa Agosti helikopta ilitua mbele ya chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648404309","data":{"timestamp":" 947648404308"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku nyingine katika mwezi huo wa Agosti helikopta ilitua mbele ya chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AGOSTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648406687","data":{"timestamp":" 947648406687"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku nyingine katika mwezi huo wa Agosti helikopta ilitua mbele ya chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HELIKOPTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648409019","data":{"timestamp":" 947648409018"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku nyingine katika mwezi huo wa Agosti helikopta ilitua mbele ya chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILITUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648413135","data":{"timestamp":" 947648413134"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku nyingine katika mwezi huo wa Agosti helikopta ilitua mbele ya chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBELE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648414874","data":{"timestamp":" 947648414874"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku nyingine katika mwezi huo wa Agosti helikopta ilitua mbele ya chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648417547","data":{"timestamp":" 947648417547"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku nyingine katika mwezi huo wa Agosti helikopta ilitua mbele ya chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHEKECHEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648419475","data":{"timestamp":" 947648419475"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliharakisha kwenda nje."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLINZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648423928","data":{"timestamp":" 947648423927"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliharakisha kwenda nje."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648426999","data":{"timestamp":" 947648426999"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliharakisha kwenda nje."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASAIDIZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648428551","data":{"timestamp":" 947648428550"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliharakisha kwenda nje."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648431477","data":{"timestamp":" 947648431477"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliharakisha kwenda nje."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIHARAKISHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648433337","data":{"timestamp":" 947648433336"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliharakisha kwenda nje."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648435100","data":{"timestamp":" 947648435100"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliharakisha kwenda nje."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648437314","data":{"timestamp":" 947648437314"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndani ya helikopta mtoto wa ndovu alifungwa katika blanketi kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648438960","data":{"timestamp":" 947648438960"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndani ya helikopta mtoto wa ndovu alifungwa katika blanketi kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648441109","data":{"timestamp":" 947648441109"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndani ya helikopta mtoto wa ndovu alifungwa katika blanketi kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HELIKOPTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648443224","data":{"timestamp":" 947648443224"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndani ya helikopta mtoto wa ndovu alifungwa katika blanketi kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648445154","data":{"timestamp":" 947648445154"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndani ya helikopta mtoto wa ndovu alifungwa katika blanketi kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648447218","data":{"timestamp":" 947648447218"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndani ya helikopta mtoto wa ndovu alifungwa katika blanketi kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOVU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648449947","data":{"timestamp":" 947648449946"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndani ya helikopta mtoto wa ndovu alifungwa katika blanketi kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFUNGWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648452069","data":{"timestamp":" 947648452069"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndani ya helikopta mtoto wa ndovu alifungwa katika blanketi kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648454138","data":{"timestamp":" 947648454138"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndani ya helikopta mtoto wa ndovu alifungwa katika blanketi kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BLANKETI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648455906","data":{"timestamp":" 947648455906"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndani ya helikopta mtoto wa ndovu alifungwa katika blanketi kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648459812","data":{"timestamp":" 947648459812"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni Ndiwa aliyekuwa katika blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648461736","data":{"timestamp":" 947648461736"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni Ndiwa aliyekuwa katika blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648464569","data":{"timestamp":" 947648464568"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni Ndiwa aliyekuwa katika blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648466586","data":{"timestamp":" 947648466585"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni Ndiwa aliyekuwa katika blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648474592","data":{"timestamp":" 947648474592"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni Ndiwa aliyekuwa katika blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BLANKETI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648476832","data":{"timestamp":" 947648476832"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na umri wa siku tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648482918","data":{"timestamp":" 947648482918"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na umri wa siku tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648484627","data":{"timestamp":" 947648484627"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na umri wa siku tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648486946","data":{"timestamp":" 947648486946"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na umri wa siku tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648488313","data":{"timestamp":" 947648488312"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alikuwa na umri wa siku tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947648488407","data":{"timestamp":" 947648488407"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_063650"," gameId":" 8c657e49-796e-4449-9215-93f60fbe4e70"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na umri wa siku tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}